President Adam W. Herbert Speeches, 2003-2008 C344
Indiana University Archives
- Speeches, 2003-2008 (Box 1)
  - Men of Color Leadership Conference, 3 February 2008 (Box 3)
  - Chancellor Charlie Nelms Installation Ceremony, 22 February 2008 (Box 3)
  - 75th Annual Alumni Awards Ceremony, 4 April 2008 (Box 3)
  - Presidential portrait unveiling, 1 May 2008 (Box 3)
  - Miscellaneous untitled andspeeches, undated (Box 3)